[{
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "62f71d877824c682ccce7998"
    },
    "question": "I spoke to ____.",
    "question_id": 1,
    "answer": "her",
    "options": {
        "1": "she", 
        "2": "her"
    }
  },{
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "62f71d877824c682ccce7999"
    },
    "question": "Where ____ you come from?",
    "question_id": 2,
    "answer": "do",
    "options": {
        "1": "do", 
        "2": "are"
    }
  },{
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "62f71d877824c682ccce799a"
    },
    "question": "What time does she ___ up?",
    "question_id": 3,
    "answer": "get",
    "options": {
        "1": "she", 
        "2": "get"
    }
  },{
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "62f71d877824c682ccce799b"
    },
    "question": "Where ___ he live?",
    "question_id": 4,
    "answer": "does",
    "options": {
        "1": "do", 
        "2": "does"
    }
  },{
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "62f71d877824c682ccce799c"
    },
    "question": "I am not ____ this film.",
    "question_id": 5,
    "answer": "liking",
    "options": {
        "1": "liking", 
        "2": "enjoying"
    }
  },{
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "64579cbc008f2391444da43a"
    },
    "question": "I am seeing her ____ three o'clock.",
    "question_id": 6,
    "answer": "at",
    "options": {
        "1": "in", 
        "2": "at",
        "3": "on"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "64579cbc008f2391444da43b"
    },
    "question": " Easter is ___ March this year.",
    "question_id": 7,
    "answer": "in",
    "options": {
        "1": "in", 
        "2": "at",
        "3": "on"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "64579cbc008f2391444da43c"
    },
    "question": "She's ____ work all day today.",
    "question_id": 8,
    "answer": "at",
    "options": {
        "1": "at", 
        "2": "on"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "65579cbc008f2391444da43a"
    },
    "question": "I go ___ by bus.",
    "question_id": 9,
    "answer": "home",
    "options": {
        "1": "home", 
        "2": "to home"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "65579cbc008f2391444da43b"
    },
    "question": "Do you like it?",
    "question_id": 10,
    "answer": "Yes, I do.",
    "options": {
        "1": "Yes, I like.", 
        "2": "Yes, I do."
    }
  }
]